Chloe, I thought that was Gabe's car.
What a surprise. I haven't seen you since...
Since my dad was fired from his job at the plant.
How's he doing?
Hanging in there.
I don't think he ever expected to be doing the human resources shuffle this late in his career, but...
He's a good man. I'm sure he'll land on his feet.
Actually, he sent out dozens of resumes and hasn't even gotten a nibble.
Look, I know this is way above and beyond the call,
but my dad said you always kept your ear real close to the ground.
Do you think somebody could be sabotaging his chances at getting a new job?
Chloe, you know I'd do anything for Gabe, but...
Lex is opening some projects none of us want anything to do with.
Trust me, your dad would be better off to put Luther Corp far behind him.
Like when we diverse society, we'd say,
I hate the stuff you guys do, and that's my thing.
If he's making fun of me, I'm gonna subscribe to your page.
We're both friends.
I'm Joe.
I'm Bobby.
We're just friends.
You can call Love to psych me with Earl concealers...
between my name and the resident's account.
Wait, you're casting yourbet on me, too, right?
We did this once to improve y'all body and allez...
Why are you schon?", I was wondering my place in Australia.
I didn't ever even see you.
any other act.
Shit.
I'm sorry.
I need a decontamination crew in section 1978.
Send a security team.
You got a visual?
All right, band, disperse your side.
You got it!
Down there!
Hey!
Hold it right there!
Now, with the crew, make some noise with me!
Hey, move it!
Oh!
Somebody save me!
Let your warm hands break right through me!
Don't care how you do it!
Just stay!
Stay!
Come on!
I've been waiting for you!
Just stay!
Ooh!
I made this whole world shine for you!
Yeah!
Come on!
Chloe!
Hey!
I've been trying to break through to Planet Chloe for two halls now!
Yeah, I guess I've had a lot on my mind.
Speaking of which, please tell me I can cross your Teacher of the Year in a minute.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do it.
I don't know.
Yeah, I can't do it!
Okay.
I'm going to have to cross your Teacher of the Year interview off my to-do list.
Um, well, I called, and I left a message, but she didn't call me back.
Clark.
Okay, Clark, I understand that Mrs. Taylor is like Fort Knox when it comes to her private
life, but journalism isn't about sitting back and waiting for someone to hand you the truth.
Sometimes, you have to actually work for it.
And sometimes, timing is everything.
Okay, Clark.
Now go, and remember, no comment is not an option.
Mrs. Taylor, I was wondering if we could set a time for your Torch interview.
It'll be painless, I promise.
Actually, Clark, I'm really busy this week.
Oh, but Mrs. Taylor, ten minutes, tops.
How about before lit class?
Does that work for you?
No, I'm printing a pop quiz.
Because I watched TV last night instead of prepping for class.
Did she really just say that?
Hey, Pete, are we still on for tonight?
Oh, yeah. I gotta drop some stuff off for my mom,
but I should definitely be home in time for tip-off.
Another lovely evening huddled around the electronic hearth.
Yeah, and since Pete's supplying the big screen,
I gotta go.
I got dinner.
What? Clark Kent in the kitchen?
What's on the menu?
Clark's gonna run to Metropolis to get us some shark dogs from the stadium.
What? Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Back up. You mean to tell me that Clark is driving six hours
to pick up a couple of hot dogs?
Well, when Clark goes supersonic, he can make the round trip in ten minutes.
He's kidding.
How that нашей
you
How that
I feel a little bit good about that.
〇 if you like melo to say that. I've been having a little problem getting people dedicated to video talk, in the brauchencomics, so this might be important to tell you about some messages we're shooting.
Thanks.
Thanks for dropping by.
Which of your obsessive-compulsive fixations is behind today's summons?
I understand there was a, um...
an incident at the Smallville plant last night, correct?
A false alarm in the old wing.
Already taken care of it.
By scrambling the hazmat team?
Just a precaution.
Or a wild overreaction.
Unless, of course, a chemical agent had actually been released.
Hmm?
I'm curious, Dad.
Why the sudden urge to play micromanager?
Because I'm concerned.
I'm concerned about you, Lex.
You're not deliberately concealing things from me.
Are you?
We all have our secrets.
We scrambling.
We all have secrets.
You know that as long as I have a knife and some begun to read,
I don't just go,
I followed him over and did this and did it!
Are you telling me you have one too?
Just now.
Fine, I admit I was wrong,
buчик.
Whatever.
We're going, to go.
üzerad.
Okay, well, so far we have student accolades,
testimonials, everything except for Mrs. Taylor herself.
Well, Chloe, if she doesn't want to talk,
maybe we should just let it go.
Hi.
Oh, hi, Chloe.
Hey, Mrs. Kent.
Are there more in the truck?
Yes, sweetheart, thank you.
I never got a chance to thank you
for the flowers you sent after Jonathan's surgery.
Oh, of course. How's he feeling?
It's been really difficult.
He's depressed and angry.
I worry that when he comes out of this,
he won't be the same man I married.
I'm sorry.
How is Clark handling all of this?
Oh, of course.
He feels responsible for Jonathan's condition.
How could he possibly be responsible
for Mr. Kent's heart attack?
It's not. It's his biological father's.
He's the one who drove Clark to Metropolis last summer.
Mom.
Where do you want these?
Clark,
you found your biological father
and you didn't tell me about it?
She meant figuratively.
Um, you know,
coming to grips with the fact
that my real parents didn't want me,
um,
played a part in what happened last summer.
Let's pick this up tomorrow.
Okay.
Bye.
I can't believe I...
I told Chloe about Jor-El.
I don't...
I don't know what happened, Clark.
Mom, it's okay.
I don't think it's just you.
I think something has happened to Chloe.
I...
I don't...
I don't think it něm Talk on and on about Teresa's scars.
I don't think anybody else can do that.
I don't know.
Talit просто niet umumen ...
and Κά dissem во butcher Wild,
heum imperius af ir
What happened to him,
in a totally new style?
His...
I'm very good at that.
It's hard to make yourself scarce in Smallville.
Actually, I'm here because of Chloe.
Have you noticed anything different about her?
I don't want to cross the roommate boundaries,
but this guy called for her yesterday when she was out.
An old co-worker of her dad's.
From Luther Corp?
Yeah, and he sounded really upset.
He was wondering if she'd taken his security card.
Klepto-Chloe?
That doesn't sound like her.
He said that whoever stole it
broke into a lab at the plant two nights ago.
Mrs. Taylor?
Hi, Mrs. Taylor.
I'm sorry to be pulling the 60 minutes card,
but I'm crushing the deadline here.
Can we just pop this off really quick?
Only because I know you'll never let me off the hook.
It must be pretty cool having the best teacher in school as a mom.
Uh, yeah, I'm kind of used to her being the best at everything she does.
Okay, we'll just start with the obvious.
Um, what do you like about teaching?
I enjoy the students.
Okay. Any downsides?
Always having to hide the truth.
I'm sorry?
The truth about what?
That Mrs. Taylor doesn't exist.
My real name is Mary Ann Lewis,
and I've been running from my past since 1972.
I don't understand. What did you do?
I was part of a radical group.
We planted explosives outside a bank in Seattle.
What?
We were just trying to make a statement.
But one of the guards came in early,
and when the bomb went off...
Mrs. Taylor, are you saying you're wanted for murder?
I... I just drove the car.
I swear I... I never meant for anyone to die.
Mom, what are you saying?
I should have told you this years ago.
I'm so sorry.
Okay, Mrs. Taylor.
No! Get away from her!
Okay? Just leave us alone!
Come on.
I'm so sorry, William.
I should have told you.
I just couldn't make myself.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Congratulations, Chloe.
Within 24 hours, you managed to take off the entire school.
Wow, you don't earn your press pass by making friends.
Don't you think the police should be handling this?
Clark, I uncovered a murder.
With your new ability.
You broke into the Luther Court plant the other night, didn't you?
Something happened?
Well, there may be some journalistic genes behind this baby blues after all.
Polly, for some reason, people are telling you things they don't want you to know.
And it's not a joke.
No, but it is every reporter's dream.
Rebecca, when the entire geometry class got C's on the final,
how is it possible that you aced it?
Oh, I swiped the answer key the day before the test.
You're not gonna tell anybody, are you?
Mindy!
Hey, Mindy!
You're always so upbeat.
Does anything bother you?
Are you kidding?
Do you have any idea how hard it is to cheer for a losing team?
Mindy, what are you talking about?
Doug, if you could take anyone to prom, who would you take?
That'd be Fitz.
Thomas Fitzpatrick the quarterback?
Wow. I didn't expect that one.
Hey, it's cool. It's off the record.
My God, Clark, this is amazing!
Can you imagine the kinds of stories I could break?
I mean, I could crack the mystery that is Clark Kent.
What do you keep hiding from me?
I can't believe you just asked me that.
I'm not gonna lie.
And you didn't answer.
Everyone else would have.
What are you so afraid of, Clark?
That I'll get behind that armor and finally uncover your secret?
Clark, last time I checked, this area is restricted.
Hey, Lex.
I'm sorry about just walking around, but the outside door was unlocked.
Actually, it looked broken to me, but I'll have a word with my security people.
Want to tell me why you're here?
I'm worried about a friend.
That friend wouldn't have happened to break into this lab a few nights ago, would they?
Clark, why didn't you come to me?
Huh.
Last time I did that, I had my conversations hand-delivered to the FBI.
Clark, whatever deal I've made with the feds, your family is strictly off limits.
I was kind of hoping you might return the favor.
And you might tell me what you were doing down here.
It wasn't me.
Lex, there's something happening to my friend.
And...
And what were you working on down here?
An old project of my father's.
He was trying to salvage something from his failure.
Then where is everything?
I decided to cut my losses.
Clark, we didn't get far enough to gauge the potential side effects.
If this friend was exposed to anything here, there could be a serious health risk.
Now, it's hard for me to help unless I know who it is.
parksourcer.com
How could you print this?
Thanks to you, my mom had to go into hiding.
The police are looking for her.
I'm sorry, William.
But I just printed the truth.
I mean, I can't be held responsible for that.
Check it out now...
...you've ruined my life.
Was it just me, or did I completely clear out the lunch crowd?
No, it was you.
Ever since you turned the torch into your own personal gossip column,
no one can stand being around you.
Yeah, at least you're still talking to me, right?
Right for now.
Okay. What's that about?
I applied to the Paris School of the Arts.
They have a full-time high school program,
and if I get accepted, I start in the summer.
Wow. I guess I'm out of the loop.
When did you decide this?
I've been thinking about it for a while now.
Everyone has their families, you know,
and I'm not sure where I fit in.
But I always thought that we were your family.
Oh, come on, Chloe.
I know what you and everyone else are.
Everyone else thinks of me, that I'm driven and self-involved.
I just can't wait to get out of here and go somewhere where people don't judge me.
I never said anything like that.
You never had to.
Why have you never talked to me about this?
Because I couldn't trust you.
Chloe, thanks for coming.
Yeah, well, I only have a minute.
Clark just called me about a story that broke at the hospital, so...
Then maybe you can just give me the, uh,
abridged version of your field trip to Luther Cork the other night.
Let me guess.
Uh, somehow, no one can resist telling you the truth.
Are you looking for an apology?
No.
Chloe,
I want you to use your gift to help me get back the weeks my father stole from me.
Lex,
I don't think your dad would go to such extremes to destroy those memories
if they didn't pose some sort of a threat to him.
Maybe you should just leave it alone.
Why do I get the feeling you know more about this than you're letting on?
I don't know anything about that.
But I do know that because of you, my dad can't get a job.
So why would I help you?
Because my father's the one who ordered his dismissal.
You know that's the truth, don't you?
Meaning that my family's future is just one chess move
in the endless game of one-upmanship played by you and your dad.
It's not a game, Chloe.
You're the only one who can get me the truth.
Why do you keep doing this to yourself?
Why can't you just walk away from your father?
Because he won't give me the only thing I've ever wanted from him.
And that would be?
I want him to love me.
Mary
也
It's over.
I can't tell you how but I was thinking.
I don't feel like doing anything for one day.
Lobster.
You did it, Ca tenga que tentar, pero simplista.
Sí,る
變了
Cro reasoning,
pero loco.
I think it's making you sick. Some sort of truth gas.
What, you wanna explain the vice grip on my arm?
Yes.
I can take a hint, Clark.
You want me to get out of here before the human lie detector shows up.
Hey, Pete.
Chloe.
No, wait. Now, enough is enough.
Everyone seems to be on the runaway from Chloe bandwagon today.
Why you?
I'm trying to stay away from you so I don't tell you the truth.
Chloe, remember that story that I called you about?
Yeah, we can talk about this story later, Clark.
Right now, I wanna know why you guys are playing such a zone defense on me.
What is the big secret, Pete?
I'm in love with you, Chloe.
I've been waiting to do that ever since the first day that I met you.
I'm not playing any more.
Okay, whoa, Pete.
Um, why didn't you tell me this sooner?
Because I knew the way you felt about Clark.
And I never saw the point.
Pete, wait.
Chloe, listen.
If Clark's right and there's something wrong with you, then take care of it.
Please.
Chloe?
Are you okay?
I need some help.
Please.
What's her name?
Chloe.
Chloe?
We're gonna take you down to exam three.
Now, Chloe, have you had enough to eat today?
Yeah, it's a little windy these days.
I'm gonna go.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
I'll be right there.
Clark.
I've been looking for you.
They arrested Mrs. Taylor.
I know.
It's been all over the Internet.
So long as you're online, you want to ask Jeeves how long it takes to die of embarrassment?
Pete.
How come you didn't tell me how you felt about Chloe?
It's not like I ever had a chance with her.
What would make you say that?
Because I'm always standing next to you.
I understand.
I got myself into trouble.
Oh, come on, Clark.
As far as long shadows go, you're the dark side of the moon.
Why are you looking through Chloe's files?
I'm worried about her.
She was working on a story about a Luther Corps project called Levitas.
This retired military doctor, General Jonah Doyle,
claims he was part of the first test five years ago.
Sounds like a crackpot.
It's our only lead.
Well, everything looks normal.
I'll be right back.
That's very dangerous information for you to have.
Why did you ask me that?
That's not important.
This is.
Of course I did, for their life insurance.
I have your entire confession recorded on my voicemail.
And the only person that has the password is me.
So if I were you, I would reconsider my father's employment situation.
I'm impressed, but unfortunately,
I don't respond to blackmail.
But, you know, this isn't what's gonna get your father's job back.
So you're going to have to give me some information.
And what would?
Information from an especially intransigent source.
Does the source have a name?
Two, actually.
Jonathan and Martha Kent.
But you need only ask one question.
Why would I ever do that?
Because I know that you have a special place in your heart for their son.
And it's killing you that he's hiding something from you.
And we both know that this may be the only opportunity
you'll ever have to find out what that is.
.
And what exactly is it that you want to know?
Where did Clark Kent come from?
You need a lesson in manners.
I'm here to talk to you about the Levitas project.
I know that Luther Corporal was a civilian contractor when you were in charge.
They've resumed the experiment.
Lionel Luther sent you?
No.
I'm here because I need to know how the drug affects you.
How it affects people.
Over there.
We were trying to create the ultimate interrogator.
Why did you stop?
I balked over safety issues.
Luther retaliated by arranging for a disappointing psych report.
And a dishonorable discharge.
Mr. Doyle, a friend of mine stumbled into the Luther Corp lab.
It was continuing the Levitas research.
I think she was exposed.
Is your friend showing any symptoms?
She's been having headaches.
And my guess is your friend will be dead by morning.
Dead?
That's why I suspended the project.
We suspected the gas would work.
But the toxicity levels were off the charts.
Is there anything that can help her?
Just before the project went down, I was working on a possible counteractant.
The results wereGA.
You know, I left her cancer.
The doctors sent me a bank note.
The work was called.
I will meet her this afternoon and pass out.
Give me pamphlets.
You don't change?
No.
You're never gonna change.
I thought the doctor in hospital would help me get in.
чисто
Excuse me. I'm looking for Chloe Sullivan.
So are we. She left without being officially discharged.
Clark, what a surprise.
Is it?
I know about your human truth serum.
The Levitas Project.
Levitas? Levitas?
I think we abandoned that project five, seven years ago.
You're lying.
That's a provocative accusation, Clark.
Especially coming from you.
I don't believe you're here just to check on Chloe's health.
What'd you do, get her to work for you again?
Ask more questions about me?
Whatever I ask her to do, Clark, is in search of the truth.
She might die.
You couldn't care less?
Come on.
Hello?
Chloe, it's Clark.
Listen, you have to get back to the hospital right now.
What you have might kill you.
You're just saying that so you can stop me.
Stop you from what?
Clark, do you know what it's like to look at your best friend every day
and know that he is lying to you?
I can't do this anymore.
Chloe?
Chloe, talk to me.
Chloe, are you all right? Chloe, talk to me.
Listen, you have to let me help you.
Chloe.
I warned you to leave us alone.
My mother doesn't deserve to be in jail.
Chloe?
Clark, I'm at the Coughlin Bridge. Please help me.
Chloe!
LAUNDRY!
unpre-
PREVIOUSLY
PRESENT
PLEASE
DEATH
I'm sorry.
Chloe, it's gonna be okay.
That's it. No need to call back.
Two invitations to your office in one week.
I should be flattered.
You should be more careful.
In the future, if you want to reactivate one of my old projects,
I...
Son, all you have to do is ask.
If you made more of an effort to keep me informed,
I wouldn't have to resort to subterfuge.
I am trying to understand, Lex,
why you would be so desperate to learn the truth
that you would resort to using a dangerously unstable drug.
Well, I guess the truth has never really held much merit for you.
I'm losing my patience, Lex.
You are constantly defensive with me.
Now tell me, damn it,
what is it you want from me?
It doesn't really matter, Dad.
I'm never gonna get it.
Chloe.
How are you feeling?
A little shaky.
But I'm totally truth serum free.
Whatever you put fiction into my chest
not only kick-started my heart,
but also relieved me of any levitas in my system, so...
That's good.
Did you hear what happened to William?
Yeah.
Between his mother's past and her arrest,
he took quite a hit.
I never meant to hurt him.
His mom's the one who should have told him.
So...
That's the thing about the truth.
It's bound to come out sooner or later.
I guess it's my turn to come clean.
When you found me on the bridge, I was on my way here.
I was gonna ask your parents all the questions you would never answer.
It was really hard.
That's why I에r joking around.
Would you...
I wanna know what sit t0me t0me is forced to happen.
I'm very sorry, I'm upset, Sy Ну-j strategist.
I'm mistakes, I'm honesty.
Okay
Alright, let's go.
Wait!
Get away from me, do you understand?
I don't wanna hear that again.
It's okay.
You're going after the truth.
Chloe, there's nothing wrong with that.
Unless it hurts the people you care the most about.
I'm just afraid that one day I'm gonna push too hard
and I'm not gonna get the chance to say I'm sorry.
Today's not that day.
Clark, thanks for coming by.
Is everything okay?
I haven't gotten many phone messages from you lately.
Yeah, um...
I've been wanting to show you this.
Paris?
I sent you my application last week.
I don't understand.
I'm leaving.
Ana, if this is because of me...
No. No.
Because of everything.
You know, I'm beginning to feel like I need a fresh start.
Well, what about your life here?
What about all your friends?
Well, maybe I'll wind up in Smallville eventually,
but I don't think I can be happy
wondering if there's something else out there.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Because I...
I didn't want anyone to talk me out of it.
And the truth is,
I knew you were the only person that could.
I know.
that's gone and that's it no need to call back
you